Guide to the Records of the Alumni Federation of New York University, Inc. RG.40.7
New York University Archives
Records of the Alumni Federation of New York University, Inc.
1919-1995
1919-1940
New York University Archives
Alumni Federation of New York University, Inc
RG.40.7
20.5 Linear Feet in 19 boxes
The Alumni Federation of New York University was incorporated in 1921 and oversaw the involvement of alumni within the University, hosted events and activities, and administered the Alumni Fund. Awards and honors like the Great Teachers Award were given out by the Alumni Federation to individuals for their achievements and contributions to the University. The Alumni Federation also published newsletters and magazines like the "Alumnus." Materials in this collection include meeting minutes, correspondence, budgets, and memorabilia related to special events and alumni relations.
Conditions Governing Access
Administrative records and unpublished reports of New York University are closed for a period of 20 years from the date of their creation. Access to files spanning multiple years will be opened to researchers based on the date of the most recent materials. Board of Trustees records are closed for 35 years from the date of creation. Materials related to personnel, grievances, job and fellowship searches and applications, and all files that fall under the federal Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA) are permanently restricted. Additional restrictions may apply to other materials in this collection. For questions regarding specific restrictions, please contact the University Archives.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Materials were transferred to the University Archives in multiple accessions in 1995 and 1996. The accession numbers associated with this collection are 96.005, 96.015, 15.011.
Arrangement
Contents are arranged topically by series. Series I, II, and III are arranged topically within series and chronologically within topical groupings. Series IV is arranged alphabetically.
Series are as follows:
I. Administrative Materials
II. Alumni Federation Activities
III. Affiliated Alumni Groups and Activities
IV. Correspondence
Historical Note
The Alumni Federation of New York University was incorporated in 1921. Officially, the Alumni Federation united what had previously been separate alumni groups from the different schools and colleges of the University. Prior to the formation of the Alumni Federation, the General Alumni Association existed but with little or no mandate to coordinate the administration of alumni activities. The Alumni Federation Board of Governors was organized with 21 members from the different alumni groups, with the largest schools contributing the most representatives. By 1940, amendments to the Alumni Federation constitution replaced the Board of Governors with a Board of Directors and increased its membership. Representatives to the Board were chosen based on a "Class" system, where larger associations, in Class A, contributed more representatives and had more power on the Board than Classes B and C.
The Alumni Federation oversaw the involvement of alumni within the University, hosted events and activities, and administered the Alumni Fund. Awards and honors like the Great Teachers Award were given out by the Alumni Federation to individuals for their achievements and contributions to the University. The Alumni Federation also published newsletters and magazines like the Alumnus.
In the 1980s, the relationship of the Alumni Federation and the University became strained. The University desired to have more control over the Federation's fundraising efforts, especially in engaging with younger alumni and connecting with alumni outside of the New York metropolitan area. The University requested, after a special review, that the Alumni Federation staff director report to the President of the University in addition to the Federation's Board of Directors. This request was made to justify the $2.7 million in annual assistance the University gave the Federation. In January of 1985, the Alumni Federation decided to become an operationally independent organization and by that autumn, it was no longer recognized and its activities no longer endorsed by the University.
By 1995, the Alumni Federation had been significantly restructured and was mainly administered by alumni from the 1940s, 1950s, and 1960s. The last Board of Directors minutes in the collection date from June 22, 1995.
Scope and Contents
Records include meeting minutes, correspondence, budgets, 60th anniversary commemorative plates and memorabilia related to special events and alumni relations. The bulk of the materials comes from the office of the Alumni Federation Secretary Benjamin A. Ross. The materials date from 1919 to 1995, but the bulk of the collection dates from 1919 to 1940.
Correspondence.; Reports.; Minutes (administrative records); Memorabilia.; New York University. Graduate School of Business Administration. Alumni Association; New York University. Washington Square College of Arts and Science; New York University Dental Alumni Association; Tompkins, Leslie J. (Leslie Jay), 1867-1952; New York University. College of Arts and Science. Colleges of Arts and Engineering Alumni Association; Kingsley, William; New York University. Alumni Association; Voorhis, Harold O.; Jones, Theodore Francis, 1885-1968; Kimball, LeRoy Ellwood, 1888-; Badger, Philip; Draper, A. S. (Andrew Sloan), 1848-1913; Chase, Harry Woodburn, 1883-1955; Brown, Elmer Ellsworth, 1861-1934; Clyne, James F.; Fernald, Henry D. (Henry Barker), 1878-1967; Briesen, Fritz; Broderick, Joseph; Hendershot, W. Raymond; Garvin, Edwin L.; Kent, Fred I., 1869-1954; Irwin, John V.; Onderdonk, Charles D.; Makay, Alexander F.; Patterson, William Morehouse; Roberts, Vincent; Ross, Benjamin A.; Saunders, Richard P.; Sommer, Frank H. (Frank Henry), 1872-1957; Washburn, Earle L.; New York University. Society for the Libraries of New York University; New York University. School of Law. Alumni Association; New York University. School of Commerce, Accounts, and Finance. Alumni Association; New York University. School of Education. Alumni Association; New York University. College of Medicine. Alumni Association; New York University. College of Engineering. Colleges of Arts and Engineering Alumni Association
- Series I: Administrative Materials
  Scope and Contents
  Series I includes annual reports, minutes, lists, and articles of incorporation related to the founding of and the administrative functions of the Alumni Federation.
  - NYU Alumni Association Annual Report, 1918-1919 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - NYU Alumni Federation Rules of Procedure, Articles of Federation, 1920-1922 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - NYU Alumni Federation Certification of Incorporation, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - NYU Alumni Federation Certification of Incorporation Amendments, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - NYU Alumni Federation Increase in Number of Directors and Amended Incorporation, Bylaws, and Rules, 1941-1991 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - NYU Alumni Federation Board of Directors, Minutes & Reports, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - NYU Alumni Federation Board of Directors, Minutes & Reports, 1922-1925 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - NYU Alumni Federation Board of Directors, Minutes & Reports, 1926-1927 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - NYU Alumni Federation Board of Directors, Minutes & Reports, 1928-1935 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - NYU Alumni Federation Board of Directors, Minutes, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - NYU Alumni Federation Board of Directors Special Accounting Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - NYU Alumni Federation Board of Directors, Minutes, 1967-1969 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - NYU Alumni Federation Board of Directors and Members, Minutes, 1981-1985 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - NYU Alumni Federation Board of Directors and Members, Minutes, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - NYU Alumni Federation Board of Directors and Members, Minutes, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - NYU Alumni Federation Board of Directors and Members, Minutes, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - NYU Alumni Federation Board of Directors and Members, Minutes, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - NYU Alumni Federation Board of Directors (1 of 2), 1930-1935 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - NYU Alumni Federation Board of Directors (2 of 2), 1930-1935 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Alumni Federation Past Presidents 1921-1985, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - NYU Alumni Federation Board of Directors 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - NYU Alumni Federation Directors - Class A 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - NYU Alumni Federation Directors - Class B 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - NYU Alumni Federation Directors - Class C 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - NYU Alumni Federation Directors - Class D 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - NYU Alumni Federation Committees 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Series II: Alumni Federation Activities
  Series II includes financial records; lists of clubs, officers, and directors; surveys; reports; correspondence; awards; and memorabilia related to the activities of the Alumni Federation.
  - Medallion Alumni Society 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Meritorious Service Awards Committee 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Presidents of the Alumni Association 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Recipients of Director Emeritus Award 1966-1984 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - NYU Alumni Associations and Clubs, Officers and Directors 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Alumni Federation "Transition", 1984 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Alumni Federation Budget, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - NYU Alumni Federation Officers and Directories 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Alumni Directory Survey, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - NYU Alumni Fund, 1929-1930 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - NYU Alumni Fund, 1931-1932 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - NYU Alumni Fund, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Alumni Scholarships, 1921-1926 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Alumni Service Corporation, 1978-1981 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Alumni Service Corporation Incorporation Documents, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Alumnus Magazine - American Alumni Council "Continued Education" Series, 1933-1935 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Alumnus Magazine, 1931-1937 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Alumnus Magazine Advertisers, undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - The American University Club of New York, Inc., 1929-1931 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Auditors' Reports, 1922-1924 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Cayuga Press Correspondence, 1929-1933 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Cayuga Press, 1931-1934 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Cayuga Press, 1934-1937 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Graduate Group, Inc. (1 of 2), 1931-1934 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Graduate Group, Inc. (2 of 2), 1931-1934 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Graduate Group, Inc., 1933-1935 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Graduate Group, Inc., 1935-1936 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Graduate Group, Inc., 1934-1937 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - "Grid-graph" Materials, 1926-1931 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Loomis, Suffern, and Fernald Accountants, 1928 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Medallic Art Company, 1932-1936 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Motion Picture Committee, 1919-1920 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - New York University, 1920-1936 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Post Master, 1923-1926 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Society for the Libraries of New York University, 1934-1935 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Alumni Day Mailings, 1920 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Carnival Dinner, NYU Alumni Federation, October 16th, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - NYU Centennial All-Alumni Dinner, March 1st, 1932 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Centennial Commencement, 1932 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Chancellor Brown Testimonial Dinner, May 3rd, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Chancellor Chase Welcome Dinner, October 31st, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - L. Jay Oliva Inaugural Reception, November 19, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - NYU Alumni Authors and their Publications, 1926 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Alumni Associations' Awards 1951-1982, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Honorary Degrees 1850-1984, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Alumni Meritorious Service Award Recipients through 1988, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Gallatin Associates Medal 1957-1988, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - New York University Medal 1956-1981, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Presidential Citation 1957-1982, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Alumni Fund 1927-1928, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Commencement Attendance Totals 1933-1980, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - NYU Club Officers 1956-1982, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Alumni Trophy Selectors 1959-1968, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Bobst Awards in Arts and Letters 1982 and 1983, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Great Teachers Award Program Administrative Files, 1957-1977 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Great Teachers by Year/School from 1959 to 1991 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Great Teachers 1978 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Great Teachers 1979 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Great Teachers 1980 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Great Teachers 1981 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Great Teachers 1982 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Great Teachers 1983 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Great Teachers 1984 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Great Teachers 1985 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Great Teachers 1986 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Great Teachers 1987 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Alumni Federation 60th Anniversary Plate, 1985 (Box 17)
  - Alumni Federation 60th Anniversary Plate, 1985 (Box 17)
    ID Number: 299. Description: Alumni Fed. 60th Anniversary. Creator/Donor/Subject: Quan, L. King.
  - Purple Alumni Federation t-shirt, undated (Box 18)
  - Metal Loving Cup, 1913-05-17 (Box 19)
    ID Number: 98. Description: Metal Loving Cup, awarded to earliest represented class (1843). Creator/Donor/Subject: Alumni Federation.
  - Purple and gold Alumni Federation commemorative plate, undated (Box 19)
  - Alumni Federation Study Lounge dedication certificate, undated (Box Shared University Archives 042, Folder 13)
- Series III: Affiliated Alumni Groups & Activities
  Series III includes reports, published proceedings, alumni records, correspondence, and ephemera related to alumni groups and activities affiliated with the Alumni Federation.
  - NYU Men in Advertising Club, 1929-1932 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - NYU Men in Finance Club, 1931-1936 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration Alumni Association, 1938-1939 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Institute of Business (1 of 2), 1928-1929 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Institute of Business (2 of 2), 1928-1929 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Institute of Business, 1929-1930 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Proceedings of the First and Second Annual Meetings of the Institute of Business, 1928-1929 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Proceedings for the Third Annual Meeting of the Institute of Business, 1931 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Addresses from the Institute of Business Meeting on Distribution, 1931 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Institute of Business, Problems and Trends in Distribution (1 of 3), 1931 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Institute of Business, Problems and Trends in Distribution (2 of 3), 1931 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Institute of Business, Problems and Trends in Distribution (3 of 3), 1931 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - 3rd Annual Federation Finance Forum - Oct. 31, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Colleges of Arts and Engineering Alumni Association, 1922-1923 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Arts and Engineering Alumni Association, 1924 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Loose papers - Arts and Engineering, 1924-1928 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Arts and Engineering, 1921-1927 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - 1890 Arts and Engineering, 1927-1930 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - 1893 Arts and Engineering, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - 1894 Arts and Engineering, 1924-1927 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - 1900 Arts and Engineering, 1925 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - 1904 Arts and Engineering, 1925 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - 1905 Arts and Engineering, 1923-1929 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - 1906-1915 Arts and Engineering, 1922-1932 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - 1917-1928 Arts and Engineering, 1924-1931 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - 1929 Arts and Engineering, 1928-1931 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - 1930 Arts and Engineering (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - 1931 Arts and Engineering, 1930-1931 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - 1932 Arts and Engineering (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Arts and Engineering Alumni Association, 1932-1934 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Arts and Engineering Midwinter Reunion 1934 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Arts and Engineering Spring Alumni Day - June 2, 1934 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Arts and Engineering Spring Alumni Day - June 8, 1935 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Arts and Engineering Dinner - Feb. 11, 1935 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Arts and Engineering Alumni Association, 1936-1937 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Arts and Engineering Spring Alumni Day - May 16, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Arts and Engineering Dinner - Feb. 20, 1936, 1935-1936 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Arts and Engineering Activities, 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Arts and Engineering Dinner - Feb. 24, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Arts and Engineering Dinner - March 2, 1939 (1 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Arts and Engineering Dinner - March 2, 1939 (2 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Engineers Club, 1934-1935 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - School of Commerce Alumni Association, 1923-1932 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - School of Commerce Classes '02, '03, '05 through '12, 1924-1925 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - School of Commerce Classes '14, '15, '16, 1924-1928 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - School of Commerce Classes '17, 1924-1929 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - School of Commerce, Accounts, and Finance Alumni Association Dinners and Minutes, 1913-1922 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - School of Commerce Alumni Association, 1924-1925 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - School of Commerce Classes '18, '19, '20, 1924-1928 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - School of Commerce Class of '21, 1924 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - School of Commerce Class of '22, '23, 1924-1927 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - School of Commerce Class of '24, 1924-1927 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - School of Commerce Class of '25, 1925-1927 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - School of Commerce Class of '27 Dinner and Silver Jubilee, 1927 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - School of Commerce Class of '28, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - School of Commerce Class of '29, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - 1929 School of Commerce Alumni Association Dinner (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - 1930 School of Commerce "Senior Hop", 1929-1930 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - School of Commerce Alumni Dinner May 2, 1935, 1935 May 5 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - School of Commerce Reunion Dinner May 7, 1936, 1936 May 7 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - School of Commerce Class of '13, 1930 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - School of Commerce Alumni Activities, 1935-1937 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - School of Commerce Activities, 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Dental School Class of '05, 1930-1931 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Dental School Classes of '14 to '19, 1930-1931 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Dental School Alumni Activities, 1927-1928 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Dental School Clinic and Dinner 1929, 1928-1929 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Dental School Alumni Days 1929 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Dental School Clinic and Dinner 1930 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Dental School 1931 Meeting (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Dental School Dinner and Alumni Day 1931, 1930-1931 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Dental School Alumni Dinner 1933 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Dental School Alumni Days 1933 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Dental School Post-Graduate Courses, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Dental College Alumni Association, 1931-1933 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Dental College Alumni Association, 1934-1935 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Dental College Alumni Association, 1935-1936 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Dental College Alumni Association, 1936-1937 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Dental College Alumni Association, 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - School of Education Alumni Association, 1924-1935 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - School of Education Alumni Association, 1930-1934 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - School of Education Alumni Association, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - School of Education Alumni Association, 1935-1936 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - School of Education Alumni Association, 1936-1937 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - School of Education Alumni Association, 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Doctors of Philosophy Club, 1931 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Doctors of Philosophy, Graduate School Alumni Association, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Doctors of Philosophy Club, Graduate School Alumni Association, 1932-1934 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Law School Class of 1893, 1899-1932 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Law School Class of 1894, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Law School Class of 1897, 1922 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Law School Class of 1898, ca. 1923 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Law School Class of 1899, 1924-1925 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Law School Class of 1900, 1924-1928 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Law School Class of 1902, 1926-1928 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Law School Class of 1905, 1931 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Law School Class of 1909, 1935 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Law School Class of 1910, 1924-1925 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Law School Class of 1914 to 1917, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Law School Class of 1918, 1924-1927 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Law School Class of 1919, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Law School Class of 1920, 1923-1925 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Law School Class of 1921, 1924-1927 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Law School Class of 1922, 1924-1931 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Law School Class of 1923, 1924-1925 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Law School Class of 1924, 1925-1929 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Law School Class of 1925, 1925-1927 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Law School Class of 1926, 1929 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Law School Alumni Association Annual Dinners 1912-1927, 1912, 1923-1928 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Law School Alumni Association Dinners 1928-1929 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Law School Alumni Association Dinners 1931-1936 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Law School Conference on Debt Relief Laws, 1935 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Law Dinner, March 16, 1937, Waldorf Astoria Hotel (1 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Law Dinner, March 16, 1937, Waldorf Astoria Hotel (2 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Law Dinner, March 9, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Law School Activities, 1936-1937 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Law School Activities, 1938-1939 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Law Dinner, May 10, 1939 (postponed) (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Law Alumni Arbitration Luncheon, February 23, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Medical College Alumni Association, 1933 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Medical College Association Activities, 1935-1936 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Medical College Association Activities, 1935-1936 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Medical Alumni Notices, 1936-1937 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Medical College Association Activities, 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Medical College Association Activities, 1938-1939 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - School of Retailing Alumni Activities, 1930-1932 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Retailing Class of 1926 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Veterinary College Alumni Association, 1919-1925 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Veterinary College Alumni Activities, 1920-1925 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Veterinary Dinner-Dance, May 7, 1931, 1925-1931 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Washington Square College Class of 1919, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Washington Square College Class of 1920, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Washington Square College Class of 1921, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Washington Square College Class of 1922, 1923, and 1924, 1924-1925 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Washington Square College Class of 1926, 1927, and 1928, 1926-1929 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Washington Square College Alumni Activities, 1923-1929 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Washington Square College Alumni Activities, 1938-1939 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - NYU Letter Club, 1936-1937 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - NYU Letter Club, 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - NYU Letter Club Activities, 1929-1933 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - NYU Letter Club Basketball Dinner, 1934 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Carnegie Tech Football Game, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Carnegie Tech Football Game (1 of 2), 1930 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Carnegie Tech Football Game (2 of 2), 1930 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Alumni Activities - Football, 1932-1936 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Football Coaches Dinner NYAC, April 19, 1934 (Box 6, Folder 11)